ofwpinoytambayan.su 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy - OfwPinoyTambayan.su

The purpose of Privacy Policy is to ensure users that you are browsing at the safe place. We care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we consider your protection important. We never ask for any data or anything. If anybody asks from you anything relating to our site you can contact to us and complain us with all information from our Contact Us page.

We use outside advertisement organizations to show advertisements on our site. These advertisements may contain treats and are gathered by the advertisement organizations, and we don’t have admittance to this data.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

In short we take extra regarding other sites to provide you safe browsing and better user experience and we never ask for your personal information. Our purpose is just to provide entertainment to all Filipinos from all over the world. In case of any Issue you can write us by using our [Contact Us](http://ofwpinoytambayan.su/contact-us/) Page.

Regards,

Admin  
ofwpinoytambayan.su  
http://ofwpinoytambayan.su
